Guide to The Other Pages: directories, 1994-2007 MS2229
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
The Other Pages: directories
1994-2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Guenther, Mark
MS2229
0.75 Linear Feet
This collection contains directories with both businesses and service agencies operating within the Washington metropolitan area. The directories date from 1994-2007.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mark Guenther of Aviance Marketing, 2007 (Accession 2007.049)
Historical or Biographical Note
The Other Pages is a business and service directory for the Lesbian and Gay community in Washington, D.C. The directory is published by Aviance Marketing. From their website Aviance Marketing describes itself as... "a full service marketing and design firm and publishers of guides to lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender people living in major metropolitan cities throughout the Mid Atlantic Region. It is with these guides that our expertise in acting as a conduit between the LGBT community and businesses both local and national that wish to reach out to the LGBT community has developed. " Aviance produces The Charm City Pages for Baltimore and The Freedom Pages for Philadephia.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains directories with both businesses and service agencies operating within the Washington metropolitan area. The directories date from 1994 to 2007.
Washington (D.C.); Lesbians -- Washington (D.C.); Gay men -- Washington (D.C.); Lesbian and gay experience; Business Directories
- The Other Pages, 1994 January - June (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Other Pages, 1994 July - December (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Other Pages, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Other Pages, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Other Pages, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Other Pages, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Other Pages, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Other Pages, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Other Pages, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Other Pages, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Other Pages, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)